sgbikemart.com.sg 2019-10-09

# Privacy Statement - SGBikemart

By using this website,  ** _www.sgbikemart.com.sg  _**, (hereinafter called the “Website” or “Site”) you, the user, (hereinafter called “you”, “your” or “user”) are agreeing to be bound by the current version of the terms of use of the Site and you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to, the terms, conditions and provisions of this Privacy Statement. 

**OVERVIEW**

SGBM PTE, Ltd., (hereinafter called “SGBM,” “we,” or “our”) is the owner and operator of the Site and recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information we collect from you.  Subject to the terms set forth herein, SGBM is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personal information.

**PURPOSE**

This Policy explains how SGBM collects, uses, stores, shares and protects information, including personal information. SGBM is committed to collecting, using, storing, sharing and protecting your personal information responsibly. By using SGBM’s website, you consent to the collection of personal information.  We may use your personal information with third parties without your consent; therefore, if you do not want such information shared with third parties, you must not use this site and its services. Information that is provided will be used, stored and shared for the purposes set forth herein.  This Policy covers both online and offline activities, including information that we collect through this website and any other information we may receive from you. 

**COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

What information do we collect?

Depending on how you interact with SGBM, we may collect from you various types of information, which are described in more detail below. In some instances (and unless we say otherwise below), we may combine one type of information with another, and store them together in our records. Other than as set forth herein, we strive to limit the amount of information we collect and store to that which is necessary to provide you the relevant services. SGBM uses such information for all legal purposes and to provide products and services to you.

**a) Personal Contact Information.**

SGBM collects personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, your name, mailing address, email, motorcycle registration number, chassis number, engine number, vehicle number plate, and telephone numbers (home, cell, etc.) entered on the Website. We typically collect personal contact information for registration activities, product orders, customer service and customer feedback.  The personal information you provide may also be used in connection with cookies and web beacons (discussed below) to improve your experience while using the Site and its Services, including remembering your preferences, customizing content or advertising you may see. We may also email you information concerning products, or additional services, which we think may interest you.

**c)   Non-personal Information.  **  
In addition to the personal information, described above, we may collect the following non-personal information without limitation: i) “Cookies”: A “cookie” is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system, ii) “Internet Protocol Address” or “IP Address”: An “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you are on the Internet. When you request pages from our Site, our servers log your IP address, iii) “Web Beacons”: A “web beacon” or “clear gif” is a small graphic image on a webpage or web-based document that a website uses to determine information about a user.  The reason for collecting such information is to generally improve the Site and your ability to use it.   Cookies can control the type of advertising that is displayed on your browser. Cookies and web beacons can track the date and time you used the Site, your language preferences, and other data that help make your web navigation experience easier and more convenient. We, or our service providers, may use your IP address when you access the Site to assist with delivery of geographically targeted advertisements.

**b)   Payment Information.**

This includes any information that you use to make a purchase, such as your credit/debit card and/or Stripe details (cardholder name, card number, expiration date, etc.), as well as check information, or other forms of payment (if such are made available). This also includes the billing name, billing address and phone number associated with your form of payment. We only collect payment information for purchases.  If you create an account with us, your payment information (along with your order history and other related preferences) may be stored under your account.  Among other services, we are offer a voucher program, as well as other services and products.  In order to purchase these services or products or to participate in the voucher program, you will need to provide the personal information, described above, including, but not limited to, your name, billing address, credit/debit card and/or Stripe information and phone number, because this information is needed to complete a purchase.

**c)   Technical Computer Information.**

This includes any information about the computer system, or other technological device, that you may be using to access the Website. We typically collect this information through the use of automated technologies, such as cookies and web beacons. Examples of technical computer information may include your computer’s IP address, operating system type, and web browser type. If you access our Website via a mobile device such as a smartphone, the collected information may also include your phone’s unique device ID, location, and other similar mobile device data. Technical computer information is not typically associated with your personal contact information.

**d)   Website Usage Information.**

This includes information about how you use and navigate our websites and applications, including which links you click on, which pages or content you view, and other similar information or statistics about your interactions with the Website, or links associated with the Site, (e.g., date and time of visit, which site you came from, etc.). This information is captured using automated technologies such as cookies and web beacons, and may be collected regardless of the device you may be using (computer, smartphone, tablet, etc.). Website usage information may be associated with your personal contact information.

**e)   Customer Feedback.**

This includes information that you voluntarily share with us about your experience in using our products, information and/or services, including our Website. Examples may include unsolicited comments and suggestions, testimonials, or other feedback about what you may have liked (or disliked) about your experience in using our products, information or services.

**f)   Customer Generated Content.**

This refers to any content that you create and then share with us by uploading it to our Website, if permitted. Examples may include photos, videos, personal stories, or other similar media or content.

**g)   Other Information.**

This refers to any other information that we might need to collect for the specific SGBM form, feature, or other service you are using or requesting. What this information might include will vary depending on the method of collection and the specific purpose(s) for which the information is being collected. Please see Section “How do we use your information?” for more specific examples.

**h)   Email Correspondence**

We may collect information from you if you correspond with us via email. For example, if you send an email to customer service, we may obtain certain information about you (such as your contact email address).

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

The following describes the various purposes and features for which we might collect and use your information, and the different types of information that might be collected for each. Please note, however, that not all of the uses listed below may be relevant to you.

**a)   Order Fulfillment**

We may collect and use your information to process and ship your orders, and to inform you about the status of your orders. Depending on how you make a purchase, this could involve the collection and use of certain personal contact information, payment information, account login information, and/or information related to your purchase (such as products ordered). This could also involve the ongoing storage of your payment information to allow for easier checkout on future purchases.

**b)   Website Personalization and Convenience**

We may collect and use your information to personalize your experience and save you time when you visit our Website. This is typically done through the use of automated technologies (such as cookies) that collect and remember certain account login information, technical information, and/or previous website usage information. For example, we might remember your login ID or username, so you can quickly login the next time you visit our site or so you can easily retrieve the items you previously placed in your shopping cart.

**c)   Marketing Communications**

We may collect and use your information to send you marketing communications, such as catalogues, email communications, and SMS text messages. These communications may inform you about new products, events, special discounts, and other news and special offers. Sending you these communications mostly requires the collection and use of certain personal contact information and limited demographic information (such as zip code). In some instances (such as for text messaging programs), this may involve the use of your precise geographical location (obtained from your mobile device) so that we can send you location-based offers. You can always opt-out from receiving marketing emails or text messages by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in each such communication. Please note that even if you opt out from receiving marketing communications, you may still receive other communications from us, such as order confirmations, and other important announcements (e.g., product recalls, privacy policy changes, etc.).

**d)   Other Uses of your Information**

To comply with applicable laws and regulatory requirements.   We are required to respond to valid legal inquiries from law enforcement or related third parties. This means that we may be required to release of your personal information in order to the law enforcement officials or to third parties to respond to a warrant, subpoena, court order, or as may be required by a State or Federal law, regulation, or statute. If at any time we suspect your use of the Site, or its information or services, is illegal or may be in connection with an illegal, fraudulent, or otherwise prohibited activity, we will not permit you to use the Site and we may inform the appropriate authorities. 

To enforce our Terms of Service agreement and otherwise manage our business.

**WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?**

We may share your information with certain companies (in the situations) described below. We do not rent or sell your information to third party companies.

**a)   Third Party Service Providers**

We may use third party service providers, including our Partners in the voucher program, to help us operate our business, or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending emails, fulfilling your product and service requests, updating information, mailing products or managing payments. We may share your information with these third parties for limited purposes. These third parties are only allowed to use your information for the specific task they’ve been hired to do, and for no other purpose. They’re also required to keep your information confidential and secure.

**b)   Business Transfer**

The consent customers have provided herein to the use of their personal information by SGBM shall also extend to any person or corporation to which SGBM may transfer its business, or in the event of a merger, sale or assignment of all or a portion of our assets or stock.

**c)   Other Disclosures**

We may disclose your personal information where required, or permitted, by law or to protect and defend our rights.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**

**a)   Security**

We are committed to keeping personal information secure. This website has security measures to help protect against loss, misuse and alteration of sensitive information, such as credit/debit card and/or Stripe information. SGBM uses security measures consistent with standard industry practice to protect that information.

**b)   Measures You Can Take**

It is also important for you to play a role in keeping your information safe. When signing up for any online account, please be sure to choose an account password that is hard for others to guess and never to reveal it to anyone else. If you use a shared or public computer, never choose to have your login ID or password remembered and make sure to log out of your account every time you leave the computer.  You may, at any time limit, or discontinue, your use of the Site, or its information and services. You must understand, however, that even after you terminate your use of the Site, we may still retain certain personal information in our databases and servers. In addition, we are not responsible for updating, or removing, your personal information contained in the lists or databases of third parties who have been provided information as permitted by this Policy.

**OTHER IMPORTANT INFORMATION**

This section provides additional policy information that is important for you to know or that we may be required to tell you by law.

**a)   Minor Children**

SGBM does not solicit, nor accept, personal information from, or market to, children under the age of 18 years.

**b)   Links to Other Websites**

This site may contain links to other sites that are not operated by SGBM. SGBM is not responsible for the contents of such other websites. In particular, SGBM is not responsible for the privacy notices, or practices, provided in such other websites. We provide such links only as a convenience and the inclusion of such links do not necessarily imply endorsement of the other sites by SGBM.

**c)   Opting Out or Modifications**

If you prefer not to receive email messages, text messages or other communications from SGBM about new products, promotions or other information, you may opt out at any time from receiving such messages by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in such email or text message you received.

**d)   Updates To This Privacy Policy**

SGBM reserves the right to make changes to this Policy. In the event we make a material change to this Policy, it will be posted here. We encourage you to check this page regularly since your continued use of the SGBM websites after any changes will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such changes.

If you have any questions about this Policy, or the practices of this website, you may contact us at the “Contact Us” section of the Website.
